Guide to the Mobilization for Youth Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Office Files
  - Training and Placement of Community Employment Technicians (Box 23)
  - Training Local Residents for Board Leadership Positions (Box 23)
  - Training Personnel in Youth Employment Programs (Box 23)
  - Training Program – Gouverneur Hospital (Box 23)
  - Training Program – Major Appliance Repairmen (Box 23)
  - Unemployment (Box 23)
  - University Outpost Project (Box 23)
  - Urban Institute (Box 23)
  - Summer Programs (Box 23)
  - Vocational and Driver Training (Box 23)
  - Welfare Problems (Box 23)
  - Which Flemming do You Read? -26 May 1959 (Box 23)
  - Workers Development Union (Box 23)
  - Reports by Mobilization for Youth (authors): (Box 24)
    - Barr -Brager (Box 24)
    - Beck. Bertram M. (three Folders) (Box 24)
    - Colangelo -Hodell (Box 24)
    - Kressler -Ruchlis (Box 24)
  - Reports by Mobilization for Youth (authors): (Box 25)
    - Thabit -Weissman (Box 25)
  - Reports by Mobilization for Youth (five unsorted Folders) (Box 25)
  - Reports by Other Agencies (authors): (Box 26)
    - Abt, C. (Box 26)
    - Aronowitz, S. (Box 26)
    - Auerswald, E. (two Folders) (Box 26)
    - Blum (Box 26)
    - Cloward (Box 26)
    - Cohen -David (Box 26)
    - Gartner -Hokenstad (Box 26)
    - Kirschner -Moed (Box 26)
    - Rein -Wilcox (Box 26)
    - Witner -Yabroff (Box 27)
  - Two unsorted Folders (Box 27)
  - Reports of people presumably not affiliated with MFY (Box 27)
  - Incomplete reports (Box 27)